Trevor de Koekkoek

Email:

tdekoekkoek@gmail.com

Senior Web and Mobile Application Consultant

A skilled full stack developer specializing in front-end technologies and in particular Angular. A problem solver with excellent written and verbal skills. Works well in a team environment or independently and as a mentor or tech lead. * Advanced web application development: Angular, GraphQL, Apollo, Bootstrap, JQuery, KnockoutJS, Sencha Touch, Sencha ExtJS, KendoUI and JQuery UI * Web technologies and tools: Webpack, Gulp, Bower, Node, NPM, Webstorm, VSCode * Layout and Responsive design: Twitter Bootstrap, CSS, LESS, SASS * Database and Cloud technologies: Scaphold.io, SQL Server, MongoDB, Parse, Azure, REST Services, Web API, Swagger * Microsoft technologies: Web API, ASP.NET MVC, LINQ, Generics, Entity Framework, Code First, migrations. * Object oriented design and patterns: MVC, Repository and MVVM, Pub/Sub * Code versioning: Git, Mercurial, SVN and TFS.

Experience

ComWeb Internet Solutions, Inc

DECEMBER 2016 - PRESENT

Software Consultant and Project Architect

Senior consultant and project architect designing an Association Management application written in Angular 2, Bootstrap, SQL Server, Entity Framework and .NET Core

Sorigo

APRIL 2016 - NOVEMBER 2016 (7 MONTHS)

Senior Software Consultant

Developed and maintained a suite of real estate applications designed for managing apartment complexes. Helped maintain an existing application written in Appcelerator while providing architecture and development on a new version written in Ionic 2.

Consultant

JUNE 2014 - JUNE 2016 (2 YEARS)

Developed a robust web portal for a medical application. The portal is used to do bulk updates to Parse.com via excel spreadsheets. The application is built using AngularJS, Entity Framework, and the C# Parse SDK and Parse Cloud Code. The application interoperates with Parse.com and is hosted on Azure.

ADP

OCTOBER 2015 - JANUARY 2016 (3 MONTHS)

Senior Software Engineer

Developing Human Resources applications in HTML5, JavaScript, AngularJS, REST and LESS

3rd Eye Software

JULY 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2015 (2 MONTHS)

Senior Software Consultant

Software development for internal application at Home Depot. AngularJS application for handling new product sample requests. AngularJS, Oracle, CSS, WebStorm.

INPO

Senior UI Developer

DECEMBER 2014 - MARCH 2015 (3 MONTHS)

Developed a resource scheduler application for the operation of nuclear power plants. The application was developed in AngularJS, WebAPI, TypeScript, Breeze and KendoUI

Bridge2 Solutions

JUNE 2014 - NOVEMBER 2014 (5 MONTHS)

UI Architect

Built travel and rewards application using AngularJS, Bootstrap, angular-ui, uirouter, JSP, CSS, .LESS, JQuery, NodeJS, Grunt. The application utilizes several webservices for searching for hotels, flights, car rentals and cruises and viewing details and adding these items to a shopping cart. Items can be purchased via accumulated rewards points.

Principal/CTO

MAY 2013 - MAY 2014 (1 YEAR)

Various Web Client applications utilizing Entity Framework, AngularJS, Web API and ServiceStack. # Built part of Oil Exploration API in ServiceStack and Entity Framework for Schlumberger (via Wintellect). # Built tax management application with Web API, KendoUI, Entity Framework and JayData. # Built Employee Admin application using Twitter Bootstrap 3, AngularJS, EF, EF Codefirst and Breeze for employee time tracking, vacation management and compliance monitoring for Covenant Data Systems, Corpus Christi, Texas.

SolTech Inc.

JANUARY 2013 - APRIL 2013 (3 MONTHS)

Senior Consultant

Built pricing application for Rollins Corporation using ASP.NET MVC 4, EF CodeFirst, JQuery, Knockout, Omu ValueInjector, KnockoutJS templates, SQL Server.

Manheim

JANUARY 2012 - DECEMBER 2012 (11 MONTHS)

Senior Software Engineer

Built automobile auction mobile application for IPhone. The application allowed users to browse cars being auctioned by state, make, model and other criteria and then to place bids on those vehicles. It was built with Sencha Touch for the front end with ASP.NET Web APIs for the REST services. Also built automobile management application in ExtJS.

Turner Broadcasting

OCTOBER 2011 - JANUARY 2012 (3 MONTHS)

Senior Software Consultant

Built Inventory tracking application for IPad utilizing ASP.NET MVC 3, JQuery Mobile.

Senior Consultant

2010 - 2011 (1 YEAR)

Senior Software Engineer

2009 - 2009 (LESS THAN A YEAR)

Kenexa

SEPTEMBER 2006 - NOVEMBER

Senior Software Engineer

Architected and developed solutions for the Talent Management division. These products were web applications for clients and included job-boards, recruiting applications, talent management and career tracking software.

Fidelity Investments Senior Software Engineer	2006 - 2006 (LESS THAN A YEAR)
Senior Software Consultant Build Fixed Income trading applications in Delphi and Ja	2001 - 2003 (2 YEARS) ava
CareCentric Senior Software Engineer	1996 - 1997 (1 YEAR)
Senior Software Consultant	1994 - 1994 (LESS THAN A YEAR)
Software Engieneer 1990 - 1991 (1 year)	1990 - 1991 (1 YEAR)
University of Southern Mississippi	1980 - 1987

Education

University of Southern Mississippi

1980 - 1987

BS, Mathematics,

Activities and Societies: Track team, Chess club